Thank you for watching!
BGM
Hello!
Oh! I think I thinned my bangs a little too much.
What do you think?
A little more curly.
Okay, I'll do that.
Like this?
I don't know. It makes my eyebrows look more dignified.
Is it that? It's the thinning of the bangs.
Not too thin today? Bangs.
It's in.
But the skin is thin.
Yeah, but if I'm on camera now...
Oh, my God, it'll take so much to cut it off.
Don't let them see.
Look at this!
Iphone case
Avocado
Avocado iPhone case
So cute!
It has a strong avocado and Korean feel to it.
It's true.
This came in this morning.
What a mess!
I love it.
Suddenly, I had a hit!
Spicy ramen noodles and kimchi!
And what's more...
It's not made in Japan.
It says "avocado" here.
But here...
but this one
It says "NUVOCADO" on it.
Ha-ha-ha-ha!
What's more...
It says "NUVOCADO" on it.
NUVOCADO!
This is so hard!
I wanna see what it says.
Isn't it "Nu"?
The first "N" in "nubocado" is...
Katakana.
and the last "Nu" is
Hiragana.
I don't get it.
This is terrible!
Nu for nubocado...
Oh no, I want it all at once!
Oh, look!
I see it.
Nu Nu Nu Nu Nu Nu Nu Nu Nu Nu Nu Nu Nu Nu
Hair and makeup are done.
Kiyo's done, too.
After I'm done.
I have some time before rehearsal.
I want to eat lunch.
What's wrong with your face?
It's true.
I'll put a mask on it.
It's just like a pin.
Kiyo, I want to eat lunch, too.
I'll have lunch.
I don't know...
It looks like it could hold a steamed bun.
A steamed meat bun.
It looks like it's going to be in there.
I'll wait
Let's wait
Bye bye. It's raining today.
It's raining today. You're not catching a cold?
No, really, don't catch a cold.
Oh, he's so cute!
Oh, you're so cute!
Imo...
Is this one of these?
It's a potato, too.
It's got a lot of personality.
And this one's a potato.
This one's a potato, too.
Strong individuality
Individuality clashes with individuality
It's not good, is it?
Oh, wait!
This is ice cream!
And oharu!
Avocado!
Avocado! It's strawberry!
All my favorite foods!
Oh, this way!
Make it popular!
Eat it!
Oh, my gosh!
Amazing.
A little straight.
Go a little forward.
Mr. Ikuro.
Mr. Ikuro's makin' man.
Iyayo.
Iyayogeyman.
Eh? It's possible.
Would you like to try?
Ready.
Yay.
Usually, it's like this.
I don't like it.
I have a pen.
No, no, no.
A little different.
I have a pen.
No, no, no.
No, no, no, no.
I have a pen.
No, no, no.
Yay, yay, yay, yay.
Game.
Yay.
Hey, hey, hey.
Awww.
Boo-boo.
It's really sideways.
It's so sideways.
Huh?
Huh.
Look at this, everyone.
Strawberry.
Oh, look at this!
congratulations
excitement
for the spring
crush, ah, spring
a fine stage 2023
wow!
amazing!
Looks delicious! My favorite strawberries!
I'm so happy for you!
I kind of want to take it down here, here.
I want this hair here.
Look, my pudding.
Huh? Oh, no! One p.m.!
I'm so happy! I'm happy today!
Congratulations!
I'm coming in!
It's raining!
Tokibara?
What?
Rain!Rain!
Rain! Rain!
Rain!
It's so cold today!
It was so cold in New Carne.
Oh, my God!
Oh, my gosh!
It's amazing!
It's like a band's house!
Wow!
Woah!
This is the first time we've been next to each other.
Hehehe.
Heh heh heh.
Amazing. It's like a figure.
Amazing.
Huh? But it's not raining right now.
It's not raining.
It's just the way it is.
But, you know, if it rained...
It's all over, isn't it?
It's Moro. Moro.
We're in trouble.
Are you okay?
I'm wet.
But I'm looking forward to getting wet.
It's gonna get cold. The wind and the water.
It's absolutely freezing.
It was a fan. It's hard work.
It's like there's not much more to do today.
I'll stop.
Someone tell me.
Stop it!
I still have a little bit more to do,
There's still time for drama.
Right. What if I told him I can go now?
Huh!
You mean, if I say so?
Can I just say that?
No, shut up.
We can go.
Okay, you two, let's get started.
Yes, sir. Please do.
Let me be the first to greet you.
One, two, three, four, five, six.
Smile to the hearts of our staff.
We are the super thrilling publicity.
Please give us your best wishes.
Please do.
Please give us your best regards.
JR East stations that appeared in 1987 are No. 1 after Tokyo Station
JR East station that appeared in 1987 is No.1 after Tokyo station
Surely someday I'll decide not to cry
Why must I press my heart
Why can't you take my eyes away?
My heart is aching
I can't get any closer
I don't want you near me anymore. Previous stage.
No, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no, no.
Thank you for watching.
It's raining, folks. It's raining.
Even though we have lots of sunny girls.
The band members are sunny girls.
I am a snow woman.
I'm a winged woman.
I'm so annoyed with snow.
Do you want to eat at 1 p.m.?
I'll eat.
You guys want some?
Coffee.
Oh, sorry.
Looks good.
It's hot.
Wait. Takoyaki, too.
I want some takoyaki, too.
I want some.
What is shaomai?
Shumai is shrimp?
Shrimp?
What's inside?
Two pieces.
It's really delicious.
I love the surroundings.
Yay! Takoyaki.
A lot.
Listen, everyone.
I may have said this before,
There are some rains that never stop, right?
I sing about bringing smiles that become light,
I think this is the main theme of my song.
I think this is my main schmello,
I think it's my main hobby, my quaint melody.
I'm sure,
I'm delivering a smile,
If it were in the middle, it would be higher than this.
I can't harmonize,
I can't harmonize, and I'm sure that's true.
I think so too.
Miz King came through.
It's cute. I love it. The Miz King.
It's so silky. I want everyone to know.
Sarasara.
Look at my hair. Look at my hair.
Isn't it pretty?
Thank you. See you later.
I'm off.
Five minutes before the show.
Five minutes before.
Is my bangs bad? Too thin?
Is Julien's too thin?
Why? Can't you see it? The bangs.
Your bangs are thin. Very thin.
Thinner than Hiyori's.
Oh, no. Five more minutes.
Five more minutes.
Let's go downstairs.
I'll do my best. Bye bye.
It's done.
I'm off.
It's Osaka. It's Osaka.
I'll do my best with the band.
I'm going to work hard in a plastic house. I'll be there.
I'll do my best.
Today is the "Tokimeki Spring Sunny Stage 2023" of Chotokimeki Advertising Department.
Give me LOVE, or else I won't go! Thank you very much for coming to the show,
Thank you very much.
This is Hiyori Yoshikawa, aka Hiyori of Super Tokimeki Green!
This performance will be standing reserved seats, and you can cheer for us in the standing room!
Oh!
Please wear non-woven masks even when voicing
There are no restrictions on the duration or volume of your voice in your seat, but we ask that you do not
However, please refrain from raising your voice in a way that interferes with the performance or disturbs other audience members.
Please refrain from using masks in your seats. And excessive jumping is prohibited.
No jumping!
The show will begin shortly.The show will begin shortly.
I love how excited everyone is.
We're really looking forward to it, so please wait just a little bit longer.
Please wait a little longer.
Yes, thank you very much.
End of shadow announcements.
Shadow announcements end.
Hanami, Julia, Coco, Karuko, Aki, Hiyori, and the super-tokimeki natural.
Knock-knock!
Good night.
Thank you for your hard work.
It's not raining?
No, I'm afraid not?
Isn't it amazing?
That's what I'm talking about.
I've never done this before.
Good luck.
Try not to slip.
Be careful.
It's slippery.
Good night.
Yes, please.
A lamppost that's broken. A rendezvous. Trust your heart.
You can't hear your voice
Ah, next year's town, I'll never let go of your hand
It's too late for that now, don't you think?
The street lamps have been cut off You can't hear me, can you?
Yes, speaking of Ao of the Cho-TokiMe Center
I'm Kanamin, a.k.a. Kanamin
Yes, I'm Kanamin... Kanamin, that's me.
So, aren't you all amazing?
I really didn't step on it.
Surprise!
It's sunny and warm here at the Tokimeki Center, isn't it?
I'm sure it's going to stay that way.
I'll be happy if we can create a fun live show together.
Let's have a great time together today!
Let's have a great time today!
Hi, it's sunny here.
It's so hot right now!
It's so hot!
It's going to rain, but even if it rains, I think it's going to be a lot of fun.
But even if it rains, I think it will be a lot of fun!
Let's prove that a live concert with time difference is a lot of fun even if it rains or shines!
Thank you very much!
I'll be there!
Shake your hearts all over the place
In the sky in the sky
Wow, wow, wow, wow
Deep in my heart, I keep hoping
I can't be quiet just yet
Time is still youth
Ready when you are
Step! Step! Jan!
Keep smiling till you go, till you go
Time is still youth
Ready when you are
Step! Step! Jean! Jean!
La La La La La La La La La La La La La La
That's good! Let's hear more from you!
Good! More!
I can't hear the staff
Oh, no!
I can't hear the staff.
Oh, I have to practice my pick-tock.
Please enjoy with no music!
I really want to see you all like this in angsty,
I'm really happy that you've taken all kinds of measures with hops and so on, and it's one time I'm really happy.
We will continue to do our best to be a group that everyone wants to meet,
I will do my best to grow more and more,
We will do our best to grow even more, so please continue to support us.
Thank you very much for coming to see us today.
This was your first one-more live concert in Osaka since the beginning of 2023,
How was everyone?
I was prepared for more rain during the show,
I was prepared for a lot more rain during the show, but I was surprised to find out that sometimes it doesn't rain even though there is a 100% chance of precipitation,
I was amazed at the power of the specially selected sunny woman.
I think everyone may be able to get tougher from now on,
Please be careful and return home without losing wind.
Thank you very much.
It's been a while since I've done a Koi Dashina concert in Osaka,
It's been a long time since I've done a Koi Dashina concert in Osaka, but it was so hot and I really loved it.
Thank you so much for giving us so much love.
It's raining, but it was cloudy,
It was cloudy, though,
Did it clear your mind?
Yes, it did.
I think it's best if everyone's hearts are clear,
I'm very happy.
I was happy to be able to make another precious memory with everyone like this.
Thank you very much for today.
I really appreciate you all coming to see me today,
Thank you so much for coming to see me today.
I think you probably got cold in your T-shirts,
So soak in the bath a lot,
I hope you all enjoyed soaking in the bath, eating delicious ramen noodles, takoyaki (octopus balls), and shumai (steamed pork dumplings),
eat delicious shumai (steamed pork dumplings), and eat delicious pork buns,
I hope you will get well.
Please be careful not to catch a cold.
Thank you very much.
I love you all.
It's raining like crazy,
It was my first time to perform in the rain,
I was so nervous,
I was so nervous, but I didn't know it would be like this in the rain.
It was so cool,
It was very cool and I felt fresh and different from usual.
I know it must have been hard for you all to sleep so well,
I'm sure it's hard for everyone to get a lot of sleep, but I woke up and went home,
I know it must be hard for you to sleep well, but I hope you will wake up and go home, and let the lingering feelings of excitement that you may have experienced today recharge you,
Please stay with us and sing with us.
Thank you so much for today.
We had fun even in the rain, didn't we?
That means it doesn't matter what the weather is like.
It was proved today that the specially selected live concert is a lot of fun even if it rains.
So, you may be getting cold,
We will continue to warm your hearts,
I would like to enjoy the show until the end so that everyone can go home with a true feeling of joy.
Thank you very much for your support today.
Don't catch a cold!
Hi, everyone!
Can you go on?
We can't let the rain beat us!
Oh, shhhh! Well then, we'll break your hearts!
Listen to this! Youth Heart Series!
Yay, yay, yay!
Thank you very much.
Thank you! And Fabrin!
Yay!
Yeah!
Fabryn!
Fabryn, what do we do?
Yeah!
Fabryn, you can't get through!
Can we go through?
Fabryn, we'd better stop!
Fabryn, no!
Thank you very much!
You're so cool!
You drew a cool guy.
Thank you so much.
I'd love to do more.
Want to take it?I'll try to take it?
Thank you very much, really.
Thank you very much.
I hope to come back with the members of this.
I look forward to working with you.
Thank you very much.
So, the Spring Spring Stage, Tokyo and Osaka performances are over.
I am glad it was over safely.
The weather in Osaka was not so good,
Because today, there is a 90% chance of precipitation.
It's 100.
Was it 100?
It was 100.
It has been 100 since yesterday.
Is that so?
And when the show started?
I was pretty terribly nervous,
I had a terrible feeling.
Rehearsals were just awful,
It wasn't like I was drenched,
I wasn't even wet anymore,
It's too amazing.
Let me see.
Was it raining?
But it was right on.
It must have been really hot.
I was sweating.
I was really impressed with Osaka.
There was so much passion,
We couldn't afford to lose,
It was like a battle of aggression against aggression,
The girls' voices were getting worse.
It was like a battle of aggression and aggression, but the girls' voices were getting worse.
Do you hear the girl's voice?
Do you hear a girl's voice coming out?
I was very happy.
Thank you very much.
Some of you got wet,
By the time you see this, it will be over,
How are you now?
Are you okay?
If everyone was watching.
I am so sorry.
Please drink lots of warm drinks,
Please be careful not to catch a cold.
I'll be back in Osaka for the tour.
I'll be back for the tour.
I'll be back.
I will do my best to do even better than before,
I will try my best to do my best,
So please continue to support us.
Thank you very much.
Subscribe to my channel!
I don't know why, but when I smile, the world seems to shine.
I can turn my umbrella around and take it easy, because otherwise I wouldn't be able to walk.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying, somewhere I'll get wet again and won't get cold.
I'm sure that somewhere someone is crying because I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with them
I want to share just a little bit of my feelings with you, so I'll go wherever you take me
Goodbye, goodbye, thank you for yesterday After the rain, the cityscape turns color
On the canvas of my broken heart, a piece of the future will be painted to guide me.
Subtitle: Kyou
I can still say it now
Whenever you're lost, remember the reason for your tears
Even if it's raining, I'll try to smile
Come on, let's go wherever you want
Good-bye Goodbye to Yesterday's Me
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a sunny sky, rainbow pools, making rainbow sounds
I play the rainbow piano
Goodbye goodbye to yesterday's me
After the rain, the streets are sparkling
My heart is like a sunny day, I'll let you play with my tears
I'm wearing a rainbow dress
Please subscribe to our channel!